Daodu Muyiwa

(Front-End Developer)

daodu.davidm@gmail.com

Daodu Muyiwa

+234 70 6593 5212

github.com/ddmuyi

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science, Microbiology, University of Ilorin, Nigeria 2013-2017

SKILLS

Languages

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- GraphQL

Libraries

- React
- JQuery
- GSAP
- Redux tool-kit
- Redux

Frameworks

- Vue.js
- Next.js
- Tailwind.css

Professional Skills

- Communication Skills
- Time Management
- Problem Solving
- Collaboration

CAREER SUMMARY

A highly proficient front-end developer with 2 years experience in building innovative technologies. Enthusistic in building pixel-perfect interfaces, implementing highly responsive software and accessible web applications using Javascript, React, Vue and other frontend tools. Keen to write clean and readable codes as well as following best-practise application architecture.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer

0xAsusu

March, 2022 - Present

- Contributing to the development of the website and admin dashboard with React.js, tailwind.css with pixel perfect implementations.
- Monitoring and improving software performance by writing debugging and performance testing (Jest)

Front-End Developer (Consultant)

OESTUDIO

September, 2021 - Present

- Collaborated with the team in developing the landing page,
 Admin, counsellor, employer and employee's dashboard for
 Sanity Hub
- Meet with the group to discuss project architecture
- Implemented responsive user interface using React and Taillwind.css

Front-End Developer

PROVIDENCE RESEARCH LTD

May, 2021 - March, 2022

- Fixed over 40+ bugs on the user interface, User experience,
 Responsiveness and Authentication in Loan-app admin dashboard
- Developed a Mobile Banking Manager(MBM) web interface using vue, vuex and tailwind.css for a client bank.
- Contributed to the development of a broker web app for an insurance company using Vue.is

Front-End Developer

PELMEDIC

April, 2019 - May, 2021

- Developed the web app using React.js
- Met with medical practitioners for insights
- Designed the infrastructure of the app with the team
- Implemented responsive and pixel-perfect designs

Website Projects

0xasusu.com

sanityhub.health

oedemy.digitals